<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Baby Names</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Closed</string>
    <string name="datos_nombres">Name Data</string>
    <string name="crear_nombre">Create Name</string>
    <string name="elegir_nombre">Choose Names</string>
    <string name="elegir_nombre1">Keys to choose</string>
    <string name="nombres_creados">Names Created</string>
    <string name="informacion">Information</string>
    <string name="salir">Exit</string>
    <string name="seleccionar">Select</string>
    <string name="nombres_cubanos">Names</string>
    <string name="nombres_extranjeros">Foreign Names</string>
    <string name="nombres_regiones">Select by Region</string>
    <string name="enviar">Send Email</string>
    <string name="favoritos">Favorites</string>
    <string name="filtrar_nombres">Filter Names</string>

    <string name="seleccionado">Selected</string>

    <string name="title_activity_pantalla_espera">Standby Screen</string>

    <string name="niñas">Girls</string>
    <string name="niños">Boys</string>
    <string name="primera_letra">First letter of name</string>
    <string name="cantidad_d_letras">Select number of letters:</string>
    <string name="cualquier_cant">Any number</string>

    <string name="compuesto">Composed</string>
    <string name="crear">Create</string>

    <string name="masculino">Male</string>
    <string name="femenino">Female</string>


    <string name="evaluenos">Evaluate us</string>

    <string name="origenes">Origin:</string>
    <string name="significado">Meaning:</string>
    <string name="favorito">Favorite:</string>

    <string name="favorito_menu">Favorites</string>
    <string name="cuentos_menu">Tales</string>
    <string name="otros_menu">Other apks</string>

    <string name="africano">African</string>
    <string name="aleman">German</string>
    <string name="americano">American</string>
    <string name="anglosajon">Anglo-Saxon</string>
    <string name="arabe">Arabic</string>
    <string name="azteca">Aztec</string>
    <string name="caldeo">Chaldean</string>
    <string name="canario">Canary</string>
    <string name="catalan">Catalan</string>
    <string name="celta">Celtic</string>
    <string name="checo">Czech</string>
    <string name="chino">Chinese</string>
    <string name="danes">Danish</string>
    <string name="egipcio">Egyptian</string>
    <string name="escoces">Scottish</string>
    <string name="eslavo">Slavic</string>
    <string name="fenicio">Phoenician</string>
    <string name="frances">French</string>
    <string name="gales">Welsh</string>
    <string name="gallego">Galician</string>
    <string name="germano">German</string>
    <string name="griego">Greek</string>
    <string name="hawaiano">Hawaiian</string>
    <string name="hebreo">Hebrew</string>
    <string name="hindu">Hindi</string>
    <string name="ingles">English</string>
    <string name="irlandes">Irish</string>
    <string name="italiano">Italian</string>
    <string name="latino">Latin</string>
    <string name="nahuatl">Nahuatl</string>
    <string name="noruego">Norwegian</string>
    <string name="persa">Persian</string>
    <string name="provenzal">Provencal</string>
    <string name="quechua">Quechua</string>
    <string name="ruso">Russian</string>
    <string name="sevillano">Seville</string>
    <string name="sueco">Swedish</string>
    <string name="vasco">Swedish</string>


    <string name="buscar">Search Here</string>

    <string name="todo">ALL</string>
    <string name="paises">COUNTRIES</string>
    <string name="origen">ORIGIN</string>

    <string name="uruguay">Uruguay</string>
    <string name="españa">Spain</string>
    <string name="eeuu">United States</string>
    <string name="italia">Italy</string>
    <string name="cuba">Cuba</string>

    <string name="escriba_alguna_letra">Write any letter</string>
    <string name="no_tiene_favoritos">You don not have favorites</string>
    <string name="no_tiene_favoritos1">You can add them in the filter option</string>

    <string name="atras">Back</string>
    <string name="siguiente">Next</string>

    <string name="creado">Created by:</string>
    <string name="version">Version:</string>

    <string name="no_reconoce_telegram">Does not recognize Telegram</string>
    <string name="copiado_portapapeles">Copied to clipboard</string>

    <!--Slide-->
    <!--Nombres-->
    <string name="n1">Search for inspiration</string>
    <string name="n2">Do a list</string>
    <string name="n3">Be aware of fads</string>
    <string name="n4">Say them out loud</string>
    <string name="n5">Follow tradition, or not</string>
    <string name="n6">Beware of quirky names</string>
    <string name="n7">Be aware of last names</string>
    <string name="n8">Check initials</string>
    <string name="n9">Names of siblings</string>
    <string name="n10">Opinions of others</string>
    <string name="n11">Unpronounceable names</string>
    <string name="n12">Be aware of the law</string>
    <string name="n13">Review the agenda</string>
    <string name="n14">Think about nicknames</string>
    <string name="n15">Do not rush</string>

    <!--Contenido-->
    <string name="c1">There are parents who, when looking for a name for their newborn,
        already have an idea of what they are going to choose, but there are those who,
        when they find out that they are going to have a child, start looking everywhere
        for inspiration .
        You can search for different media; such as books or internet sites to get a wide variety
        of options when choosing. For that, here we offer you a wide variety of names to
        choose from.
    </string>
    <string name="c2">If you already know the sex of the baby you can make a list easier,
        but it never hurts to be prepared. It does not matter how long it is, then you can go on
        debugging, the important thing is not to leave out any that you like, or that sounds good
        to you. You can do this from filters and add them to favorites.
    </string>
    <string name="c3">You can be one of the parents who look for the names that are trends, or not;
        perhaps they look for names that are not similar to any other.
        There are those who are guided by television actors, or writers, it is totally valid,
        although you must be careful with that because the name that you love today may not
        like you tomorrow.
    </string>
    <string name="c4">It can be very helpful to say the names out loud, to see how they sound,
        both alone and with surnames. This way you will notice better if they are very long,
        very short, they sound good.
    </string>
    <string name="c5">It is a tradition in many families to use the same name for generations,
        and although it is always expected to continue to be used, this is the decision of the
        parents. They may be under pressure because the baby on the way has a family name.
        But the most important thing is that above all it is a name that parents like.
    </string>
    <string name="c6">There are many ridiculous names in the world, first of all think how your
        child feels to bear a certain name throughout his life, if he can feel excluded or offended.
        Do not give your child a name that they can be ashamed of.
    </string>
    <string name="c7">It is a good idea to write and pronounce the first and last names,
        so as not to make mistakes, such as rhymes that lend themselves to ridicule,
        or make puns that make them the target of ridicule. In addition to taking into
        account if the name and surnames are long, it can be very tiresome, as well as
        if they are very short. Although this is a matter of taste.
    </string>
    <string name="c8">At the time of writing the names you can also check the initials of names
        and surnames, it would not be good if they form acronyms, shortenings, or bad acronyms.
    </string>
    <string name="c9">It is good to try your siblings names together, see if they sound good
        together, and not make the mistake of calling them the same name in different languages.
    </string>
    <string name="c10">There are those who ask anyone for an opinion, or there are those who
        keep decisions to themselves. You should keep in mind that if you start asking others
        for opinions, they will influence your decision, and you may not choose a name that
        you like, just because a friend was bothered by someone and it was called that.
        This will end up limiting your choices.
    </string>
    <string name="c11">There are those who ask anyone for an opinion, or there are those who
        keep decisions to themselves. You should keep in mind that if you start asking
        others for opinions, they will influence your decision, and you may not choose a
        name that you like, just because a friend was bothered by someone and it was called that.
        This will end up limiting your choices.
    </string>
    <string name="c12">You must take into account the legislation of the country, some other
        names may be prohibited in your country, because they may harm the person,
        or go against decorum.
    </string>
    <string name="c13">Children should not have names of exes or pets, or people you do not like,
        or can remember unpleasant moments in your life. So you should avoid these names that
        can cause conflicts or constant friction.
    </string>
    <string name="c14">Nicknames should be taken into account, because after spending so much
        time looking for a name, you end up calling him by a nickname; such as Antonio, Tony.
    </string>
    <string name="c15">
        There is time to choose the name of the baby, there are those who do not even know it
        until the moment of delivery, because they did not choose it beforehand, or they wait
        to see their child before choosing it, to be guided by how it looks. First of all,
        do not rush, lest you choose a name and then change your mind, so take as long as you want.
    </string>

</resources>